globalthinktest.com 2014-09-23

# Global Think Test From Kaspersky Lab - Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is very important to us.  We take the protection of your personal information very seriously. This policy is intended to help you understand how we collect , use  and safeguard the information you provide to us. 

By using or accessing this Website you signify your acknowledgment and agreement to the Privacy Policy set forth below. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this Website. We can revise this policy at any time by updating this posting, and your use after such change signifies your acceptance of the changed terms. Please check this policy periodically for changes. 

If you browse our Website, you may generally do so anonymously without providing any personal information.   **Please note the position with cookies.   We can only collect cookies if you agree.  By continuing to use our website, that counts as your agreement to our collection of cookies.**  
If you have given us your explicit consent, we will provide  opportunities for you to share personal information should you elect to participate. Examples of this include entering contests and sweepstakes, providing input to a market research study and requesting or downloading information or software. Use of information collected in these ways will be restricted to those purposes unless we explicitly ask your permission to use the information in another way.     
We  reserve the right to disclose user information in special cases, when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other   users of our website , or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose personal information without notice to you in response to a subpoena or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to respond to an emergency situation.  We do not knowingly collect or use any personal information from users under 16 years of age. If we become aware that such information has been obtained, we will delete it immediately. 

Please note that our Website contains links to third-party Websites. The linked sites are not under our control of, and we are not responsible for the contents or privacy practices of any linked site or any link on a linked site.   
 We may share statistical or aggregated non-personal information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. This data is used to customize our website content and advertising to deliver a better experience to our users.
